托林:在他先前严谨的蓝调音乐中.
Torien: Previously, on his strict blues.
本:等等,这是成长的烦恼!
Ben: Wait a minute, this is Growing Pains!
托林:哦,打扰一下,本,先前在他的成长的烦恼中.
Torien: Oh, excuse me, Ben, previously, on his growing pains.
谢谢,托林,
Thanks, Torien - Anyway, we just had these real crunch fish sticks.
这是德文伊中学,除了我大家都去参加舞会啦!
OK, there's this Dance at Dewey high, and everyone but me was going.
今晚我自由了,妈妈爸爸都去跳舞了,
Tonight, I boogie.Mum and dad got to the dance,
但舞会上只有他们一对父母,还有一些看门的人.
but there weren't any other Chaperones, just some old janitor guy.
老男人:德文伊中学的舞会什么也不会发生,基本上是个乏味的舞会.
Old Guy: Nothing much ever happens a Dewey Dances, basically they're nerd festivals.
音乐主播:孩子们,他讲的对,这是你们父母们的恶梦.
DJ: Thats right kids, its your mommie and your daddies worst nightmare!
本:对女孩们,迈克,
Ben: Things got off to a slow start for the girls, and Mike, Andy,
安迪和波纳来说来说事情开始的太慢啦!
and Boner were bored stiff.
波纳:是的,我再也不吃鱼片了.
Boner: Yeah, I was out of fish sticks anyway.
迈克:你还带了鱼片?
Mike: You brought them with you?
波纳:放心,我也带了口香糖.
Boner: Don't worry, I brought breath mints, too!
本:迈克那些人今晚开始看上变聪明了,他总是说等他在老些,
Ben: Then Mikes evening started to look just a little bit brighter,
他就会更明白的,现在我也理解了他的说法.
he says I'll understand when I'm older.Hah!I understand now!
女孩们则没那么幸运,德布伊准备给胸部垫些东西.
The girls weren't having much luck so Debbie decided to expand her bra size.
德布伊:你们看看这怎么样?
Debbie: Well, what'd you think?
开萝尔:难道你的肩膀以前会高些?
Carol: Didn't your shoulders used to be a little higher?
本:不就每个人都会兴奋起来的,是的,是每个人.
Ben: Pretty soon, everyone was rocking out.Well, almost everyone.
开萝尔:你来这里怎么也不跳舞?
Carol: How comes you're not dancing?
波纳:我在跳!
Boner: I am.
开萝尔:我是说你怎么没舞伴呀!
Carol: I mean with somebody.
波纳:我也不知道,那你怎么也没舞伴呢?
Boner: Oh, I don't know.Why ain't you?
本:我猜我没有告诉你当波纳和开萝尔在跳舞的时候,
Ben: I guess I don't have to tell you, when Carol danced with Boner,
天都要塌下来啦!
all Hell broke loose.
雪莉:你什么要跟波纳跳舞?
Shirley: Why were you dancing with Boner
女孩:哇!波纳!
Girls: Eeew, Boner!
波纳:我和她跳得挺开心的,没人和她跳,我挺她可怜的.
Boner: We were just dancing having a good time, I felt sorry for her!
德布伊:开萝尔,善待动物的时候已经过去了,你不记得啦?
Debbie: Carol, 'Be kind to animal week' is over, got it?
迈克:不要和她跳啦!我看不下去啦!你明白吗?
Mike: Well, knock it off man!It gives me the creeps, you got it?
本:当一切这样进行下去的时候,
Ben: While all this was going on,
爸爸妈妈发生了一些矛盾.
Mum and Dad were having problems of their own.
杰森:怎么了?
Jason: What's up?
音乐主播:背有点抽筋,老是这样的,不过不要紧,现在不怎么痛啦!
DJ: Tweaked back, goes down on me all the time!
麦琪:我能什么可以帮忙的吗?
Maggie: Is there anything I can do to help?
音乐主播:把音乐继续播着,不让没有音乐啦!
DJ: Yeah, just keep the music going, lady - or I'm out of a gig!
本:这也比不上迈克和他梦想中的女孩说话时的情景.
Ben: That isn't half as bad as what Mike heard when he talked to his dream
girl.
迈克:嘿!我叫迈克.
Mike: Hi, my name's Mike.
莉迪娅:我知道,我叫莉迪娅.
Lidiya: I know that, I'm Lidiya.
本:我和臭虫从他家溜出来去了一个秘密的地方,
Ben: What no one else knew was that Stinky and I were sneaking out of
这件事还没被人发现.今晚我们将成为男子汉,
his house to get to a secret place.
我们走吧!
This is the night you and I become men!Let's go!
臭虫:我告诉我看到了一些东西.
Stinky: I tell you man, I saw something!
本:但我现在没时间听你讲,
Ben: But I haven't got time to talk about that now,
以为最后我还要去布莱克家,那么你在等什么?
cause I've finally made it to Blackie's.So, what are you waiting for?
给我笑一个!
Show me that smile!
麦琪:是的!我们都要沸腾了,
Maggie: Yes, yes, yes, we all really starting to cook, and Wow.
节奏让我燃烧起来,我在燃烧了,
This is really burning me up.I've got to heat up.I've got to cool down.
我得冷静一下了,你们要尽情地跳啊.
Let's move this party up-and-down now.
音乐主播:我不要去医院,我要找我的推拿师,
DJ: But I don't want to go to the hospital.I want my chiropractor.
你们没听到吗?
Can you dig it?
一男人:开萝尔,你想跳个舞吗?
A Man: Carol, do you want to dance?
开萝尔:是的,我只是不确定.
Carol: Yeah, That'd be...I am not sure.
波纳:晚上好,女士们!能请你们其中的一个跳舞吗?
Boner: Good evening, ladies, per chance would any of you like to dance?
波纳:那就下次啦!
Boner: Perhaps another time.
安迪:去跳吧!波纳,你怎么不跳呢?
Andy: Come on, Boner, get in the game man.
波纳:我在喘会气.
Boner: I'm just catching my breath.
杰森:好了,现在就让我来吧!
Jason: Ok, I can take over now.
麦琪:为什么?
Maggie: Why?
杰森:亲爱的,你不记得我在大学的时候上过电台吗?
Jason: Honey, I did have a radio show in college, remember?
麦琪:当然记得,你太差劲啦!
Maggie: Of course I do.You stunk!
杰森:得了,你以前不是我很棒嘛!
Jason: Come on, you used to say I was great.
麦琪:亲爱的,那时我才十九岁,我会知道什么?
Maggie: Well, Honey what did I know?I was 19.
麦琪:我感觉如此好,如此有劲,如此轻松,如此渴望又是如此担心.
Maggie: I feel good, I feel strong, I feel loose, I feel long and funky!
杰森:我很差劲吗?
Jason: I stunk, huh?
莉迪娅:(唱歌)她是小妖精,她是小妖精.
Lidiya: (sing) She is a brick.She is a spirit.Just letting it all hang out.
我要去给我的鼻子补补妆.
I've got to go to powder my nose...
迈克:太棒了!我是说这真是个好主意.
Mike: Oh, great.I mean, yeah, good.Good idea...
莉迪娅:你哪里也不要去,你知道吗?
Lidiya: Don't you go anywhere.You hear me?
迈克:好的.
Mike: Oh, yeah.
安迪:迈克,你小子晚上的运气不错!
Andy: Oh, Mikey, you've got your hands full tonight.
迈克:是的,你说的对极了.
Mike: Oh, yeah, you could say that.
安迪:好吧!我确实希望莉迪娅能在我耳边耳语.
Andy: Well, I do wish I had Lidiya whispering sweet nothings in my ear.
迈克:耳语?不要紧的,你去吧!
Mike: Whispering?It couldn't hurt.
德布伊:好吧,这不是最倒霉的一次.
Debbie: Ok, so it wasn't one of my best ideas.
雪莉:但却是最伤心的一次.
Shelley: The sad part is it was.
开萝尔:要是想让别人请我们跳舞,
Carol: If we want the guy to dance with us,
那为什么把自己关在洗手间里?
why we are hanging in the bathroom?
莉迪娅:她是个小妖精.
Lidiya: She is a Brick.
雪莉:现在的男人竟然会喜欢这样庸俗的女人,
Shelley: That's the kind of cheap, trashy woman men go for these days!
你们能相信吗?
Can you believe it?
德布伊:让我感觉真恶心.
Debbie: Makes me gag.
雪莉:是的,看看她穿的那衣服?
Shelley: Yeah.Wonder where she shops?
开萝尔:我们还是出去吧?
Carol: Can we just go?
德布伊:等等,你在说笑吧!
Debbie: Wait, you are not any fun.
雪莉:德布伊,你的香水有点鱼腥味,
Shelley: Debbie, that perfume you have one smells like fish.
你是从哪买的?
Where did you get that stuff?
德布伊:这是你送我的生日礼物.
Debbie: It was a birthday present from you.
开萝尔:那好吧,我回家啦!
Carol: Well, I am going home.
雪莉:等等,不是你的味道,是开萝尔的.
Shelley: Wait, it's not you.It's Carol.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
德布伊:是的,你身上有股鱼口香糖的味道.
Debbie: Yeah, you smell like a fish stinks and breath-mints.
开萝尔:不可能!
Carol: I do not I do.
德布伊:开萝尔,你看和波纳跳舞很好吗?
Debbie: Carol, See what happened when you dance with Boner?
你难道想一辈子身上都有鱼味吗?
You want to spend the rest of your life smelling like the catch of the day?
本:我们成功啦,我们到了,
Ben: Made it, there it is, all right, two players,
太棒了!这就是他们说的能赢钱的东西.
that's the machine the one we heard about.The one that pays real money.
老妇人:嘿!有什么要帮忙的吗?小伙子们.
Old lady: Hi, Can I help you, boys?
臭虫:我们想要钱.
Stinky: We want money.
老妇人:什么?
Old lady: Pardon me?
本:我们想要个馅饼,
Ben: We want a pie.
把你这最好的馅饼和饮料给我们拿来.
Give us some of your best pie and a couple of cups of Joe.
老妇人:马上就好.
Old lady: Coming right up.
本:你不能那样说,偷钱是犯法的,特别是我们小孩.我们本应该去找布莱克的.
Ben: You are supposed not to say that, gambling is illegal, especially for kids, where've
you been?We were supposed to ask for Blackie
臭虫:你是说我们该去见见布莱克?
Stinky: Would we like to see Blackie?
老妇人:布莱克已经死了.
Old lady: Blackie is dead.
本:这就是最好的馅饼.
Ben: Just this is the best pie.
臭虫:我一点不饿.
Stinky: I am not hungry.
本:好吧,我承认我们现在遇到一点小麻烦了.
Ben: Ok, I admit, we've run into a little problem here.
臭虫:这是小问题!人死了!
Stinky: Little problem, the man is dead.
本:好了,别提布莱克啦!还可以再去问别人嘛!
Ben: Ok, forget Blackie.There's just got to be someone else to ask.
臭虫:问谁?
Stinky: Who?
本:你不用担心,
Ben: Ok, Look on the bright side.
现在已经是10点钟了,咱俩今晚躲在这,
Well, it is ten at night, we're on our own,
我们爸妈不会知道的.
there is not a chance in the world our parents are going to find out.
老男人:她是小妖精.你们是在值夜班吗?
Old Man: She is a birck.So, men, you working a late shift?
莉迪娅:迈克,这真是首好歌.
Lidiya: Mike, it is a great song.
迈克:安静点!
Mike: Quiet!
莉迪娅:你对我吼什么?
Lidiya: You snapped at me.
迈克:不,抱歉!我是在想我们也许该找个安静的地方,那样我们就不用讲太多的话.
Mike: No, I am sorry.I just thought maybe we can go to someplace quiet
where we wouldn't have to talk at all
莉迪娅:不说话?哦.
Lidiya: Not Talk?Oh.
迈克:是的.
Mike: Exactly.
波纳:嘿!开萝尔.
Boner: Hi, Carol.
开萝尔:波纳,你怎么样?
Carol: Boner, how are you?
波纳:再见!
Boner: See you.
开萝尔:再见!
Carol: Bye.
麦琪:这首歌是送给所有的女孩和他们的心上人.
Maggie: This one is dedicated to all the girls out there who feel the
same way about their guys as I feel about mine.
本:这馅饼真好吃.
Ben: Um, Good pie.
臭虫:我可不想起着女孩的车看你吃馅饼.
Stinky: I don't ride girl's bike for watching the pie.
本:嘿!放松点.
Ben: Hey, relax.
臭虫:你想去赌一把嘛?
Stinky: Are we going to gamble or what?
本:好的.
Ben: Yes.
臭虫:真的吗?
Stinky: How?
本:我们要先问问那些经常来的赌徒这里是什么赌法?
Ben: Ok, All we need to do is find out how this gambling thing works from someone who comes here a lot.
老男人:这星期的牛排怎么没有上星期的好吃?
Old Man: This week's pork chops weren't nearly as tangy as last week's.
老妇人:这就是上星期的.
Old Lady: Earl, those were last week's pork chops.
本:这里的东西可能在顾客来之前就做好的.
Ben: This guys probably been coming here since food was invented
老妇人:孩子们,还要什么其他吃的吗?
Old Lady: Anything else or is that it, boys?
本:我们每人再来一馅饼怎样?我要再拿一个.
Ben: Oh, what if we each have another piece of pie?
馅饼看起来不错!
Watch, I'll get it out of this guy.Pie is pretty good.
老男人:那咖啡怎么样?
Old Man: Yeah.How's the coffee tonight?
本:我喝过更好的.
Ben: Well, I had better.
老男人:在你小时候吗?
Old Man: When you were younger.
本,是的,这酒吧不错.
Ben: Yeah.Nice place.
老男人:一般啦!
Old Man: It's open.
本:不错的弹球机.
Ben: Nice pinball machine.
老男人:小鬼,是不是想要和我谈谈?
Old Man: This going to be a long conversation, Son?
臭虫:他想知道怎么用这个弹球机赚钱?
Stinky: What he wants to know is how to get play pinball for money.
本:我正想问他呢!
Ben: I was getting to that.
臭虫:你磨蹭啦!
Stinky: Not fast enough.
老男人:原来你俩也是赌徒呀!
Old Man: So you are a couple of high rollers, huh?
本:我们带了八美元.
Ben: We've got 8 bucks between us.
老男人:八美元?
Old Man: 8 bucks?
臭虫:是的.
Stinky: Yeah.
老男人:嘿!玛吉,有两位先生想玩弹球机,就按庄家规则玩吧!
Old Man: Hi, Margie, These 2 gentlemen want to play a little pinball.House rules.
老男人:那行吗?
Old Lady: Is that right?
臭虫和本:那是什么规则?
Stinky and Ben: How are the rules?
老男人:好吧!
Old Lady: All right.
臭虫和本:哇!
Stinky and Ben: Wow.
老男人:我把你们的钱换成硬币吧,这样就可以玩了.
Old Lady: I just give you boys your change in quarters and you're on your own.
本:这里有九美元.
Ben: This is nine bucks.
臭虫:九美元?
Stinky: Nine?
本:九美元,我们赚了.
Ben: Nine, we've only got!
本:放松点,想想我们今晚出来有多难!
Ben: Easy, you haven't gone through what we've gone through to get here.
臭虫:我们先溜出来.
Stinky: We sneaked out.
本:我们走了好多路.
Ben: We walked miles.
臭虫:然后我们骑着车.
Stinky: We took buses in circles.
本:还看到了恐龙.
Ben: Saw the dinosaurs.
臭虫:我骑的还是女式车.
Stinky: I Ride a girl's bike.
本:今晚爸妈刚好去参加舞会了,
Ben: And this is the one night in my entire life that my parents are going
所以我们就溜出来啦!
to be out late tonight for me to sneak out.
老男人:那么说你们爸妈还不知道你们来这里啦?
Old Man: So, your parents don't know where you are?
本:你在开玩笑吗?他们都去德文伊中学跳舞去了.
Ben: Are you Kidding, they'd freak.They are off chaperoning some goofey dancing in the Dewey High.
老男人:你难道是指托马斯·E·德文伊中学?是吗?
Old Man: Don't you mean Thomos E.Dewey High?Do you?
(唱歌)
(sing)
麦琪:谢谢,亲爱的.
Maggie: Thanks, honey.
杰森:要是你想我来接班,就喊我!
Jason: Oh, anytime you want to me to jump in, just holler.
麦琪:我可不用你来接班,我玩的很开心着呢!
Maggie: Oh, I don't want you to jump in, I'm having fun.
杰森:哦,我是担心你会累的.
Jason: Oh, just thought you might be getting a little tired.
麦琪:累?
Maggie: Tired?
杰森:好吧,你看你都放了一个晚上的音乐啦!
Jason: Well, you've been spinning records all night.
麦琪:哦,不!我的精力还很旺盛呢!
Maggie: Oh, no no, no, I have plenty of energy left.
杰森:好的,不过孩子们好像有点烦你放的音乐啦!
Jason: Ok.Kids seem to be getting a little bored.
麦琪:杰森?
Maggie: Jason?
杰森:麦琪,我不是说你工作不努力.
Jason: It's not that you are not doing a great job, Maggie.
麦琪:谢谢你.
Maggie: Thank you
杰森:你还是缺少训练.
Jason: You just don't have the training.
麦琪:杰森,我不想听你说了,我玩的开心着呢!
Maggie: Jason, I am not going to listen to you.I am having fun.
杰森:好吧,可那也很重要.
Jason: Well, that's important too.
麦琪:杰森,你只是想削弱我的自信心,
Maggie: Jason you are just try to undermine my confidence just because
那是因为你想要饭唱片.
you want to play DJ.
杰森:不过从传统上讲,
Jason: It's just that a man, traditionally,
男人是最适合做这个工作的.
is the best person for the job of DJ.
麦琪:男人是最适合的?
Maggie: The best person?
杰森:麦琪,我是指男人知道怎么活跃气氛!哈哈哈!
Jason: What I mean, Maggie, is that man knows how to be exciting, hahaha.
麦琪:杰森,可惜你没娶个男人.
Maggie: Jason, it's too bad you are not married a guy.
开萝尔:妈妈,我想和你谈谈.
Carol: Mom, I need to talk to you.
杰森:你妈妈正玩的开心呢!什么事/
Jason: Here your mom is busy having fun.What is it?
开萝尔:不,爸爸,这事很重要.
Carol: No, dad, this is important.
杰森:哦?
Jason: Oh.
麦琪:好吧,亲爱的开萝尔,你有什么事?
Maggie: Yes, Carol sweetie, what is it?
开萝尔:怎么了?
Carol: What's wrong?
麦琪:哦,是你的爸爸.
Maggie: Oh, it's your father.
开萝尔:哦!
Carol: Aha.
麦琪:你怎么啦?
Maggie: What's on your mind?
开萝尔:妈妈,我想听听你的意见,德布伊和雪莉认为……
Carol: Ok mom, see I want to need your advice, Debbie and Shelley think.
麦琪:无论我们做什么事,我们都应该好好享受它.
Maggie: When we're doing something, we enjoy it.
开萝尔:那是我的想法.
Carol: That's my thought.
麦琪:无需成为最佳的那个人,我只要开心就行.
Maggie: It's nothing to do with being the best person.I was just having a little fun.
开萝尔:我也这样想的.
Carol: Me too.
麦琪:别人怎么说你不要太在意.
Maggie: You shouldn't take care about what other people think.
开萝尔:你太对了.
Carol: You are darn right.
开萝尔和麦琪:太好了!
Carol, Maggie: Good.
开萝尔和麦琪:谢谢!
Carol, Maggie: Thanks.
麦琪:你给我走开!煽动者先生.
Maggie: Get away from there, Mr.Exciting.
莉迪娅:看看那些星星
Lidiya: Looking at all these stars...
迈克:嘘!
Mike: Hush.
莉迪娅:嘘!(他们开始接吻),这感觉真好.
Lidiya: Hush( They kissed each other) Gee, that was special.
迈克:莉迪娅,我觉得我们发展的好像太快了,我只是想我们明早彼此都不要后悔.我想现在我们最好还是回去,然后好好想想清楚.
Mike: Oh, look, Lidiya,
I think it's going to be a little too fast for me right now, ok?
I mean, erm, I really don't want to do anything that we're both going
to feel sorry for in the morning.
I mean I think I'm just get a little swept away from here and we can
both use some time to just think.
莉迪娅:想想?
Lidiya: Think?
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
莉迪娅:你这是尊重我吗?我能理解.
Lidiya: Oh you mean respect me?I understand.
迈克:好吧,那是因为我不知道怎么办.
Mike: Good, because I don't think I do.
莉迪娅:让我告诉你该怎么办吧!
Lidiya: Let me see if I can explain.
迈克:不……
Mike: No no no...
莉迪娅:哦,迈克,和你跳舞真有意思.
Lidiya: Oh Oh, Mike, it was great dancing with you.
迈克:的确,和你跳舞真是太棒啦!
Mike: It was a wonderful dancing with you.
莉迪娅:能和你谈话我也是很开心呀!
Lidiya: And it's a great talking to you too.
迈克:和你跳舞真是太棒啦!
Mike: It was a wonderful dancing with you.
今晚过得真是愉快!
You know I really had a great time tonight.
莉迪娅:我也是,到时我给你打电话,我们再谈谈.
Lidiya: Me too.I'll call you some time, and we can talk.
男学生:老师来了.
Schoolboys: The teacher!
杰森:哦,等等,
Jason: Oh, wait, I am not a teacher.
我不是老师.但作为医生,
But as a medical doctor, I'll tell you right now;
我得告诉你吸烟是不好的,这样讲,请别介意!
smoking is a leading cause - ah, never mind.
波纳,你怎么躲着我?
Boner, am I keeping you from something?
波纳:不是的,我刚好来这里有事,
Boner: No, I just came in here because I figured there'd be no girls in
因为男厕所里不会有女孩.
the boys' bathroom.
杰森:我也是.
Jason: Me too.
波纳:我能不能像男人和男人那样问你一些问题?
Boner: Can I ask you something man to man?
杰森:当然,这个房间正合适.
Jason: Well, we're in the right room is for it.
波纳:也许我们坐下来更好.
Boner: Maybe we should sit down.
杰森:不,不!波纳,是什么事?
Jason: No, no.Boner, what is it?
波纳:我说的是要是有个有趣的家伙和一个女孩跳舞跳的很开心,而他的好友们却让他马上悬崖勒马.
Boner: What would say if this guy, a pretty interesting guy, ok?
He's dancing with this girl and having a good time.
But his friends who shall remain nameless say it ain't cool.
杰森:她的好友?
Jason: His good friends?
波纳:你在开玩笑?他们是迈克和安迪.
Boner: Are you kidding, they're Mikey and Andy.
杰森:那这个人是讲你吧!
Jason: So we're talking about you, Boner.
波纳:我有所那很有趣的家伙是我了吗?
Boner: Gave it away when I said interesting guy, didn't I?
杰森:你是不是很想和那女孩跳舞?
Jason: Yeah.But you want to dance with this girl?
波纳:和她跳舞那是我整晚最开心的时候.
Boner: It's the only time I was having fun all night.
杰森:那你就不要听迈克和安迪说的,
Jason: Well then forget about what Mike and Andy said,
尤其是迈克的.
especially what Mike says.
波纳:西沃医生,你不用担心,我会好好照顾开萝尔的.
Boner: Doctor Seaver.And don't worry; I wont even think of trying anything funny with Carol.
杰森:你真是好小伙!和开萝尔?等等,波纳,你在做什么?
Jason: Ok, good boy, with Carol, wait, Boner, Wait.What have you done?
本:妈妈?
Ben: Mom?
麦琪:本,等会.我正在放唱片,你在这里干什么?
Maggie: Wait a second Ben, I'm doing the sag way here.Ben, what are you doing here?
本:妈妈,我本想骗你的.
Ben: Mom, I could lie to you.
麦琪:你不会的.
Maggie: But you won't.
本:我是不该骗你的,我没住在臭虫家,
Ben: My thought exactly.
而是到一个地方去赌钱,
You see, I didn't stay at Stinky's, I went to this place to gamble for money,
我把赢的钱买馅饼吃了,我做错了.
but I blew my wad on pie.I feel sick about it.
杰森:麦琪,不用操心,这事我来处理.
Jason: Maggie, indeed here, don't worry, I can handle it.
麦琪:杰森,本在这里.
Maggie: Jason, Ben is here.
杰森:我是杰森·西沃,现在我给大家放一首好听的歌曲,大家听了一定会喜欢的.嘿!本,你来干什么?你该呆在臭虫家里.
Jason: Hi, Ben, you're just in time to listen to this.Hi, guys, you will Jason Seaver is here.What are you doing here Ben?You should have stayed with Stinky.
麦琪:他对我们说了谎,他刚刚吃了馅饼,并且还去赌了一把.
Maggie: That was a lie.He has been out eating pie and blowing his wad.
杰森:你都做了什么?
Jason: What did you do?
本:妈妈,爸爸,我很抱歉!
Ben: Mom, Dad, I am so ashamed.
安迪:莉塔,舞会结束和你想和我们去吃披萨吗?
Andy: So after the dance, you want to go and get some pizza with us?
莉塔:我们是谁?
Rita: Who is us?
安迪:你,我和迈克.
Andy: You, me, Mike.
莉塔:当然行.
Rita: Sure.Oh...
安迪:也许我们可以下次来预定披萨.
Andy: Maybe we can order pizza another time, hum?
开萝尔:安迪,有没看到波纳?
Carol: Andy, have you seen Boner?
安迪:去男厕所看看.
Andy: Check the men's room.
开萝尔:我会去看的,谢谢!
Carol: I will, thanks.
迈克:安迪,我有件事.
Mike: Andy, I need a word.
安迪:打扰啦!我也会第二外语.
Andy: Excuse me, I am bilingual myself.
波纳:安迪,你有没看到开萝尔?
Boner: Andy, you've seen Carol?
安迪:在男厕所.
Andy: Men's room.
波纳:谢谢.
Boner: Thanks.
安迪:迈克,莉塔想去吃夜宵.
Andy: Mike, Rita is up for a midnight snack.
迈克:安迪,我不想去吃夜宵了,我想回家去了.
Mike: Oh, Andy, I'm not up for a midnight snack, I want to go home.
安迪:好吧!你刚刚还和莉塔呆在一起,怎么现在就想回家?
Andy: Well, well, you partied with Lidiya.You want to leave?
迈克:是的,现在就想走.
Mike: Yeah, now.
安迪:不,等等!
Andy: No, wait, you said something big was going to happen tonight.
你说今晚会有大事发生的,这就是我.
And it is for me too.Mike,
迈克,我是说我恋爱了.
guy, darn it, I'll just say it - I am in love.
迈克:很好,那我走会好了.
Mike: Fine fine.I walk home then.
安迪:哦,我知道了,莉迪娅不要你.
Andy: Oh, I get it.Lidiya is not buying.
迈克:不,不!是我不要她.
Mike: No no.I am not buying.
安迪:迈克,她怎么不好啦?
Andy: Mike, what is wrong with her?
迈克:很难说清楚,你不明白吗?
Mike: Well, it's hard to explain.See?
首先是她的声音.
All right, I just tell you that first, it's her voice.
安迪:她的声音?
Andy: Her voice?
迈克:事实上她不太聪明.
Mike: And actually she is not too bright.
安迪:哦,漂亮的女孩是傻瓜!
Andy: Oh, beautiful chick who is really dumb.
迈克:这事真是太糟糕了,
Mike: This just is a nightmare.
也许我不该只重外表,
All right, may looks are everything,
也许我有了更高的标准.我并不喜欢她,
maybe I got too high standards or something.I don't know.
我想说你跟莉迪娅很配,
And I don't like it,
埃迪,
but I'll I'm saying Andy is I look at the way you feel about Rita.
我真是嫉妒你.
Man and I envy you.
安迪:要是我和莉迪娅交往你会不会介意?
Andy: So would you mind if I took a shot with Lidiya?
迈克:莉迪娅?我以为你喜欢莉塔.
Mike: Lidiya?I thought you loved Rita.
安迪:我是喜欢莉塔,迈克帮我个忙,
Andy: So did I.Mike, do me a favor.Let Rita down easy for me, hum?
你去安慰一下莉塔,
She's a good kid,
好吗?你想你最了解女人了.
and I don't know anybody with more experience disappointing women than you.
迈克:安迪?
Mike: Andy?
本:然后那看门的人把臭虫送回家,把我送到这里来了.
Ben: And then that Janitor guy dropped Stinky off and brought me here.
麦琪:那真是个好故事,本!
Maggie: That's quite a story, Ben.
杰森:好了,年轻人,
Jason: Well you sit down right over there, young man,
现在你给我老实地坐这里,
and don't you move until your mother and I discuss the most appropriate
在我们想到最合理最严厉的惩罚之前,你不准离开半步.
and painful punishment?
本:我受的罪还不够多吗?
Ben: Not suffered enough?
波纳:开萝尔?她不在男厕所!
Boner: Carol?She wasn't there.
开萝尔:哦,波纳,我一直在找你!
Carol: Oh, Boner, I've been looking for you.
波纳:我也是在找你.
Boner: So have I.
开萝尔:你看,波纳,
Carol: Look, Boner, I've known you, well,
我了解你.那是因为我们已经认识好几年啦!
since I don't remember not knowing you.
波纳:开萝尔,我想……
Boner: Carol, I just want to...
开萝尔:可你一直都是我生命中最熟悉的陌生人.
Carol: You've always been the strangest person in my life.
波纳:是的,我也有这样感觉.
Boner: Well, you do?
开萝尔:此前我们一起跳舞,
Carol: And when we were dancing before,
那的确是我今晚最开心的时刻.
I was really having fun for the first time this whole miserable evening.
波纳:我也是.
Boner: Me too.
波纳:而且是千真万确的.
Boner: Exactly.
开萝尔:即便是我的朋友说我发疯了,我也不管.
Carol: And even all my friends are saying I am crazy, I don't care.
波纳:我也一样!
Boner: Neither do I.
开萝尔:虽然你有点怪,那又有什么关系呢?
Carol: So what if you are a little strange?
波纳:是的.
Boner: Yeah.
开萝尔:我只是想跳个舞.
Carol: I just want to dance.
要是你有什么不轨的企图,我就揍你.
And if you want to try anything funny, I'll duck you.
现在你还要说什么吗/
Now, what are you going to say?
波纳:坏主意?你指的是什么?
Boner: What do you call anything fun?
开萝尔:波纳!
Carol: Boner!
波纳:抱歉.
Boner: I am sorry.
开萝尔:哦,你想不想跳舞?
Carol: Oh, you want to dance or what?
波纳:我觉得我还没邀请你.
Boner: I thought I never ask.
本:好吧,我是大本,
Ben: Alright, it's Big Ben, bringing you his happy message.
给你们送上美妙的音乐.现在请大家尽情摇摆,尽情的跳吧!
Move to the groove when you've got nothing to lose.
杰森:好吧,我猜我们知道他是遗传的啦!
Jason: Well, I guess we know where he gets it.
麦琪:是我!
Maggie: From me.
杰森:是我!
Jason: From me.
莉塔:最后终于来了个称职的音乐主播.
Rita: Wow, we finally get a decent DJ.
迈克:哦,莉塔,安迪突然有点事!
Mike: Oh, Rita, look, Andy had something come up.
莉塔:真的吗?
Rita: Really?
迈克:是的,他必须得离开一下.
Mike: Yeah, he had to leave.
莉塔:我要向你坦白一件事,
Rita: Well I have a confession to make.
原先我问你和安迪要不要跳舞,
See when I asked you and Andy to dance earlier,
其实我是想要和你跳舞的.
I really wanted to dance with you.
迈克:真的吗?
Mike: Really?
莉塔:迈克·西沃.上五年纪的时候我就开始喜欢你了.
Rita: Mike Seaver, I've had a crush on you since the fifth Grade.
迈克:真的吗?
Mike: Really?
莉塔:是的,我能和你跳个舞吗?
Rita: So, can I dance with you or just sit there saying "really"?
还是这样一直坐着说"真的吗"!这看上去真是可爱!
And looking adorable.
德布伊:好了,我们已经在经历帮开萝尔啦!
Debbie: Well, we did all we could to help Carol.
雪莉:这简直是她的葬礼.
Shelley: It's her funeral.
德布伊:雪莉,我们俩事唯一没跳舞的女孩.
Debbie: Shelley, we are the only girls not dancing.
雪莉:你想去跳吗?
Shelley: You want to dance?
德布伊:当然!
Debbie: Absolutely.
迈克:请你不要把你的眼睛离开我的视线!
Mike: Keep your eyes on this guy every second.
(音乐响起)
(music)
安迪:迈克,她比你说的还差劲!
迈克:谢谢,伙计!
00:22:25,800
Andy: Mike, she's worse than you said. Mike: Thanks Man!